Don't force yourself, Ludaas.
Even sitting with that wound is agonizing.
I'll let you talk while you lie like that.
Head... Head over head.
Only...
... if you're not going to sit, I don't need your legs.
What... What the hell!
Am I going to talk while lying in front of you?
Your humble servant Ludaas would never disrespect you like that!
I understand.
Submit your report then.
Translation: Magnum357 Control: MiracA
But it's late.
Kim?
What do you mean who? I say Kurosaki!
Aren't we going to help or something?
There's no need. The enemy's soul force has long since disappeared.
Kurosaki wouldn't lose to someone of that level.
I have no intention of helping.
Are you saying so? Because I would.
N'oldu Inoue?
I was thinking how close you were with Kurosaki.
I love this side of you, let me tell you.
What is it? Don't wave!
I came!
Welcome Kurosaki! Did you get hurt?
No, I'm not injured either...
Sorry, my soul phone is ringing.
Hello, this is Yuki.
- What happened? - Thing...
Collective notice sent to all divisions.
Listen. I will give you a summary of the current situation.
Don't ask questions. What I will say will not be repeated.
57 minutes ago, 7 unknown persons infiltrated the 1st Division headquarters.
It was withdrawn 52 minutes ago.
One of the 1st Division died, but nothing happened to the Commander-in-Chief.
Meanwhile, at the Kokuryo Gate, where the 1st Division is guarding...
... an unknown person appeared.
In a conflict that lasted 182 seconds, all 116 soldiers were killed.
Deputy Commander Sasakibe was seriously injured in this conflict...
…and soon died in the 1st Division commander's room.
What's more!
Deputy Commander Sasakibe...
...he had served Commander-in-Chief Yamamato for years!
How could he have died?
Finally... the entry and exit methods of the enemies remain a mystery.
There is no sign of tampering with the spirit protection shield surrounding the Seireitei.
We think they have a mode of transportation that crosses the shield.
It doesn't get out of my head. I'll go patrol.
I-what-go!
In the?
Extreme Acceleration!
First Name! Long time no see...
... is this how you do it?
Ichigo, we're in trouble.
Help, Ichigo.
Hueco Mundo... Hueco Mundo...
It means five days.
Yes. Enough time for us and the Soul Society to prepare for war—
You are talking about the future.
And two days ago, when you went to check the border density level...
...if we continue to move forward in this direction, with Soul Society in the near future...
...the world of the living, because of the imbalance of spirits...
... will disappear. That's exactly what you said.
Lüdaas Friegen.
Are you a seer standing before me now?
Ben...
Answer me. I ask if he is a priest.
No. I am not.
On what grounds are you talking about the distant future, then?
I want to hear now.
- Boars. - Emredin!
You deserve neither praise nor punishment.
You were enough to stall Kurosaki Ichigo.
Thank you!
You did your bit. You will be the foundation of the road to peace.
- No trouble, sir? - Like what?
Arrancar soldiers...
...isn't it a valuable unit because they don't need training?
I do not care.
Finding Arrancar is easy.
Hueco Mundo is now my territory.
It's nothing more than a cornerstone of the Soul Society invasion.
Hollow World mu?
What's going on Nel? What do you mean Hueco Mundo was hacked?
by whom?
Extreme Acceleration!
I had concealed my existence until the very last moment!
You even avoided this, bravo to you Kurosaki Ichigo!
Oh sorry! You don't know who I am underneath!
Who am I to say! I...
Peaches.
Seireitei, Crematorium
Near.
I'm sorry, I gathered you at this hour.
It's not a problem. Is that true?
Konusu Hollow World.
TRUE. After losing Baraggan and Starrk...
...His Holiness Harribel became the ruler of Hueco Mundo.
But even he...
Avoid.
Quick!
Lets go!
His Holiness Harribel!
We do not know why they took His Holiness Harribel.
They took His Holiness Harribel!
Do you know who they are or their purpose?
Unfortunately.
But we know they took a lot of Arrancar.
They cornered us while we were trying to escape...
...and they caught Dondoçakka!
Kurosaki Ichigo, please help us!
Kurosaki.
It's wrong to ask. Are we going to help?
After hearing this, I cannot remain indifferent.
Kurosaki Ichigo!
Ichigo!
Don't worry...
... but this time I will not be able to help you.
At work.
I am Quincy. I can't save the Hollows or the Arrancars.
Yes.
The Quincys exist to destroy the Hollows, right?
I expected you to say that.
I thought I'd call anyway, you'd be shy or something.
Kurosaki.
Be careful.
Don't worry. We'll get through without you.
- The enemy this time... - I see...
... an interesting love is going on.
Shall I assign you to Hueco Mundo?
Your Majesty.
The locket you gave Ebern... There are signs of use.
But...
How could you come at such a good time?
Is not it certain? I was waiting outside the window for the right moment.
Garganta - I said.
It's hard not to notice that two Arrancars have fallen from Hueco Mundo.
Also, your previous fight...
...and the abnormal activity at Soul Society is more than enough for caution.
You noticed too, didn't you?
Kurosaki, the current events are all connected.
Now things got serious.
Yes, we're at the exit!
Hueco Mundo - Come on, quick!
Don't stop, keep walking!
A, we're in the air! The enemy is below us!
What Urahara Bey always does!
- How well do you know me! - We're falling!
- What happened? - It's like I heard a voice.
It can't be. Except for the dead...
... all those who stayed there are here.
- That's how it came to you. - It's possible.
It seems we go unnoticed.
Is Dondoçakka among the prisoners?
No, I don't feel spirit power. Probably in another group.
The reason they don't come back here is...
... knowing that all the Hollows and Arrancars here are dead.
- You don't see them. - It's a scary sight.
Unfortunately. It's like no one is alive.
I hadn't given in. That's their style.
Look at this.
This is the condensed soul particle flame they use.
Thanks to this, the stone and sand of Hueco Mundo, which did not burn under normal conditions, burned.
In the face of those who use a force we have never seen...
... we were completely stunned.
We had no choice but to flee.
Then those who were just taken...
They may want to use it as a vanguard.
In the worst-case scenario, they're just like the ones here...
Understood. Let's go save it.
Hold on! There is no Dondochakka there!
So what? We will save Dondochakka anyway.
What difference does it make if we save a few Arrancars on the way?
So... It's true that you're right.
Wait, don't go!
Look at this job. The Arrancars he went to rescue...
... is he not aware that he has an enemy until yesterday?
- Exactly! - You both knew.
That Ichigo is such a person.
If you can solve this problem, if Ichigo solves it...
....you asked him for help without hesitation.
Let's go too Sado!
- We... We're coming too! - Yes!
Get in line! Get your back against the wall!
Hurry up!
We'll drill you another hole or two!
Stern Ritter "J"
Looks like this guy's head.
Look, are we really going to do it? I don't think we should.
Stupid, they're going to kill us anyway!
Yeah!
Silence please! Will you live or will you die?
We'll be holding a qualifier for the Hollows and Arrancars!
Ben...
I will kill everyone one by one, starting from the right!
If anyone says "I don't want to die"...
...or if there is someone who says "I want to join you"...
... beg as if he wanted to kneel and lick our shoes!
As long as you guys survive our attack...
... you are the chosen ones who are lucky, smart and strong!
I beg you, do not waste this opportunity!
If you're going to spare my life, it's solid—
Yes, of course it's not that easy!
Those who will apply must take the entrance exam!
This elimination will determine the person who is entitled to take that exam.
For those who don't understand my explanation...
... like this, like this....
Does the Commander have any thoughts on bringing Arrancar?
There isn't any. He's not interested in Hueco Mundo anyway.
... dies like this!
- My commander! - Your time to say "commander" is too slow.
Very strange. I thought we confiscated all your swords.
Loly Aivirrne, aide-de-camp of our Lord Aizen!
Likewise Menoly Mallia!
We will not be defeated by servants like you!
- Do it. - Yes, sir!
- Shall we kill? - No.
His Majesty has asked us to bring in the brave fools.
These girls passed the exam. Punish them so they don't die.
However, I find it odd that Arrancars of this rank are adjutants.
So the person called Aizen isn't very smart.
Although, Tier Harribel, who took over the place after Aizen's death...
...he couldn't fall in love with His Majesty.
We shouldn't be surprised.
Who did I tell you not to overdo it?
May I ask who are you?
Talk back and forth about our Lord Harribel, come get to know us!
I guess the butlers are not given much information!
You took Sir Harribel while we were gone.
Don't get off your ass just because you beat those who call themselves Aizen's squire!
Mila Rose, Sung-Sun, Apacci (Three Beast)
What is this? The war has already begun!
- That's Tres Bestia's soul power! - What are you looking for there...
They take orders directly from His Holiness Harribel!
They are terribly powerful and frightening!
Moreover, they are always trying to take each other's lives like cannibalistic monsters!
If those insanely powerful monsters are here...
... get well soon to the enemy army!
- They're so scary, Ichigo! - I can't see ahead, stupid!
What, are you pulling me?
Stupid, I didn't open my mouth!
Delete that snot also!
Extraordinary.
You must not dive.
I have a suggestion for you. Surrender.
Are you stupid?
You are just empty talk!
If you surrender and join our army...
...you can work for Her Majesty with your only Tier Harribel.
Not now or later...
... you can't reach a greater happiness than this!
- What do you think we're a Four-Eyed Monkey? - Don't belittle us!
Oh, the negotiations failed?
I am in great disappointment.
1st Company Barracks, Meeting Room
I have given you the detailed report on the infiltration of the rebel army.
Thanks Akon. You can withdraw.
Yes, sir.
Yes, this time it's foreigners... Which we're nicknamed the rebel army for now.
With the invasion of this rebel army that calls itself the Wandenreich...
...the disappearance of the Hollows in the living world...
... interconnected.
Destroying multiple Hollows in the world of the living...
... caused serious imbalance of spirits.
It is quite possible that the world of the living and the Soul Society will perish.
destroying spirits...
Intelligent commanders have already understood.
Insurgent army...
…consist of Quincys.
The army is blowing their pipes.
It sounds like shooting stars.
The army stamps its feet. Like thunder.