Yuzu...
You're noisy.
I guess one hostage is enough.
Karin!
Very well.
I still have a hostage.
I've been waiting for you, Shinigami.
Karin!
Ichi-nii...
That guy...
What's... going on...
You bastard... You're the one who was
on the bank that day, aren't you?
Six years ago!
Why are you here?
Six years ago?
Ichigo, you don't mean...
Yeah...
That day, I tried to save this kid.
But... when I woke up, he had disappeared...
...and my mom was...
...my mom was...
Six years ago?
I don't remember anything that long ago.
I see, this is interesting.
The Ground Fisher...
That's its codename.
It hides itself...
...and makes the appendage growing
out of its head take human form.
Then any human who can see it...
...in other words, any human with
a soul of high spirit density...
...becomes fodder to increase its power.
That Hollow has evaded us Shinigami for over 50 years.
And its favorite meal is...
...women.
Which means...
...this thing killed my mom?
Ah, I see.
You're a lucky kid to have survived after seeing me.
At first, I may have been trying to eat you
because of your great spirit power.
But women just look so tasty.
You bastard...
There aren't many Hollows that piss me off as much as this one.
Karin!
Don't be careless, you fool!
Ichigo!
You're the only one I'll NEVER forgive!
Disintegrate, Black Dog of Rondanini!
Look upon yourself and burn; tear away your own throat!
Way of Binding, Number 9...
GEKI!
Don't disturb me!
Now then, I'm going to eat this girl.
What are you going to do?
Karin!
STOP!
So, you'll be good and let me eat you?
Karin!!
Hey...
You...
Why did you do that...
Shinigamis keep fighting the Hollows, no matter what.
Shinigamis never forgive Hollows.
Because of Hollows attacking indiscriminately...
...precious people are lost...
...and only emptiness is left.
I won't forgive that.
Protect them, spiky boy.
You understand, don't you...
Hey!
Don't tell me he died even though he's a Shinigami.
Even Shinigamis are not immortal.
The form may be different, but death is-
Wait, that bastard's sleeping...
Hey, wake up!
That's confusing!
Nee-san!
W-Whoa, this is getting jacked up.
Kon!
Take the sisters and run away!
What about you, Nee-san?
Hurry!
Yes, ma'am!
Ichigo, back me up.
Ichigo!
Rukia, stay back.
What are you saying?
This time, you mind your own business.
I'll do this alone!
Don't be ridiculous!
That thing is strong.
I told you...
It has avoided the Shinigamis for over 50 yea-
Shut up.
Please...
Don't interfere.
This is...
...MY fight!
Uh... Karin...
A-Are you okay?
It's exhausting to keep my brow furrowed all the time!
How does that freakin' Ichigo keep his face like this?!
Geez!
Too slow, boy.
Damn...
With your abilities, I' m surprised you had the guts
to tell me to stay away from your friends.
Eh, boy?
Shut up...
After mom died...
...I couldn't imagine how sad Yuzu felt...
...I couldn't imagine how lonely Karin felt...
Protect them, spiky boy.
I decided I would protect them.
I'm going to...
...beat this bastard!
Didn't your friend tell you not to be careless?
How many times now have you lunged
at your enemy without a plan?
That's the definition of "careless", boy!
Impulsive...
You're impulsive!
You sent away your comrade based on a fleeting emotion...
...and on a fleeting emotion, you lunge at your enemy.
And in this way, you will perform for
my amusement and die at the end!
Ichigo!
Stay away.
Keep away, Rukia!
I'm going to beat him.
Even if my arm gets severed...
Even if my leg gets tossed...
I'll beat him!
That is why you will die.
Because you are young, you anger easily.
Because you anger, your heart is in chaos.
And because your heart is in chaos, your blade is dulled.
It's over, boy!
You are far too young to fight with me!
Ichigo, is that...
You son of a bitch...
Even the most hardened of Shinigamis have
at least one person they could never kill.
That is absolute.
By finding that person, I have so far evaded the Shinigamis.
And for you, that person must be this woman.
That's right, isn't it Ichigo?
Ichigo!
And what of pride?
If you help him now, yes, you can probably save his life.
But...
...at the same time, it will kill his pride for all eternity.
Listen to me.
Remember this well.
There are two kinds of fights.
We must always know the difference.
A fight to defend life...
...and a fight to defend pride...
That's right...
This is a fight for Ichigo to defend his pride...
...a fight I musn't interfere with.
Don't interfere...
Don't die, Ichigo!
Ah, crap.
I fell asleep.
Damn.
Can you raise your sword to this woman?
You bastard...
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
Don't bring out... my mom's image... in a place like this!
Don't, Ichigo.
Put your sword away.
Don't kill mommy.
Please...
I told you.
Anger dulls the blade.
It will be over with the next attack, boy.
Let me pay my respects to you.
Of all the Shinigamis I've encountered, you
were the youngest, the most impulsive...
...and by far, the WEAKEST!
Ichigo!
What?!
Is that...
Mom...
That's the mother's soma.
Her wish has taken form.
Are you saying the lure remembered his mother's dying wish?
Dying wish...?
I glimpsed her earlier...
This fight's still up in the air.
Ichigo.
I'm so proud.
Dad...
...Karin...
...Yuzu...
...and you, Ichigo.
I'm truly proud to have known you.
Ichigo, live.
Be strong.
Be gentle.
And smile.
Ichigo, thank you.
Ichigo.
Mom...
That's what you were thinking that time?
Anger dulls the blade?
You may be right.
But...
You're wrong about one thing.
To beat a loser like you...
...a dull blade is more than enough!
If I were the rain...
...that binds together the earth and the sky,
who in all eternity will never mingle...
...would I be able to bind the hearts of people together?
Kurosaki-kun...
I feel like I can understand you a little bit.
Shit!
I won't forgive you!
Just a mere Shinigami!
Come back here!
Ichigo!
Stop it!
That's enough.
Neither you nor he can fight anymore.
The fight is over!
Not yet!
He's not dead yet!
I still haven't-
Ichigo!
You survived.
Ichigo...
Thank you.
He's one bad ass kid.
A Shinigami's spirit power is the same thing as his life force.
He could become a monster some day.
Well then, I'm goin' home.
I'm not crazy enough to tear apart a serious couple.
I'll just tell them Rukia-chan's reached that age.
Don't!
Okay, I'll just make something up.
Anyway, if they find out, they find out.
Buh-bye!
Sorry.
I wasn't able to avenge you, Mom.
Well, as long as you show her you're healthy,
she can rest assured on the other side.
Don't eavesdrop on your son talking to himself.
I thought you quit.
She complimented me on it when we first started dating.
"Your hand looks cool when you're smoking," she said.
Thinking about it now, that was the first
and the last time she complimented me.
So I smoke just this one day every year.
Here in front of her.
How can you smile?
Why isn't anyone blaming me?!
This is too hard!
If you'd just tear into me, it'd be easier...
Why...
Why should I blame you?
If I blamed you for Masaki's death, she'd get angry at me.
It wasn't anyone's fault that Masaki died.
It's just that...
...the woman I fell in love with was a woman
who didn't mind dying to protect her kid.
And don't forget...
...you're the man who the woman I fell
in love with lost her life to protect.
Dad...
Owww!
Live to the fullest, Ichigo.
Live to the fullest...
...age to the fullest...
...go bald to the fullest...
...and die long after I do.
And if possible, die with a smile.
Otherwise, I won't be able to look Masaki in the eye.
Don't be wishy-washy.
You're still too young to look cool carrying your grief around.
I'll be waiting down below.
You listening, Rukia?
Let me be a Shinigami for a little longer.
I want to get stronger.
More...
Stronger so I can protect them from Hollows...
...protect the people being targeted.
I'm going to beat him!
Otherwise...
I won't be able to face my mom!
Ichigo.
That was a fearsome Hollow!
This time, I was pitiful, but...
Next time, the man, the one Kon-sama will
stride over flowers and storms alike
and go full force for Rukia-onee-chan.
You don't have a line in the next episode.