N-No…
That's impossible…
I can't believe the Tres Bestia
were defeated…
A Soul Reaper with an Arrancar
on his back?
How unusual.
That being said…
I know all about you,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
The Daten that His Majesty gave us
included information about you.
You were listed
as a "Special Threat"
that we should prioritize
dealing with!
"Special Threat"?
That technique…
the Hirenkyaku.
Are you guys really Qui--?
Oh, my!
Don't tell me that you engaged us
without knowing who we were?
Very well!
In that case…
I shall answer your question.
Yes, we are who you think we are.
We are Quincies.
SQUAD ONE BARRACKS -
CAPTAIN'S MEETING ROOM
Quincies…
Well, I figured
that would be the case,
but this is quite the problem.
Where is their base of operations?
Unfortunately,
I have yet to find it…
I see…
That means we have no way
of attacking them.
I'm ordering all Squad Captains
to prepare for war.
The advance guard of the rebel army
announced that the battle
would begin in five days,
but there is no reason to believe
the words of treacherous fellows
that would launch
a surprise attack.
We must prepare for battle at once,
as fast as we possibly can!
We must not let them
get the upper hand again!
The blue skies above are hopelessly clear
At my wit's end, I feel a growing frustration
As if to laugh at us hopeless cowards
Countless eyes stare at us
This soul of mine breaks again and again
All I can do is hold it tight
Until the day it turns to ash
I've absorbed all of this sorrow
It has shaped me, painted me
But that's how we got here, right?
One step at a time, just like breathing
These countless scars on my palm
That no longer fade
Are my badge, my story
I faced the fear and shred it to pieces
And let it walk beside me once more
BLEACH: THOUSAND-YEAR BLOOD WAR
All shots hit their mark.
What's the matter?!
You can do better than this!
That's weird…
I heard that Quincies
only use bows.
What?
Kurosaki!
Inoue!
Look after Nel!
Impressive…
It makes me dismayed
by my lack of skill…
Don't worry.
Your arrows were a lot stronger
than Ishida's.
Though it's been quite some time
since I got hit with one of them.
"Ishida"?
By "Ishida,"
are you referring to "Uryu Ishida"?
You guys know about Ishida?
Uryu Ishida's Heilig Pfeil
is weaker than mine?
How odd…
That's not possible.
What do you mean?
Whoops.
Speech is silver,
silence is golden.
I've said a little too much.
Forgive me…
Now then, it's time for me
to stop fooling around.
I just received orders
from His Majesty.
Just who is this "Majesty"?
I have no need
to answer that question.
In short, it means
you are going to die here.
Now take a good look.
I'm sure you've heard
about this power…
A Quincy's final state, Letz Stile!
The Quincy secret move
that Ishida used before!
Allow me to explain…
The proper name for this form is…
Quincy Voll Stern Dich.
We've received an update
from Jagd Armee 1.
Quilge Opie is currently
engaged in battle
with "Special Threat"
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Then let's go…
Where to, Your Majesty?
Isn't it obvious?
An imperial order from His Majesty
to the Stern Ritter.
All Stern Ritter are to
immediately get equipped
and assemble at
the Gate of the Sun.
Repeat…
All Stern Ritter are to…
The Wandenreich is going to…
invade the Soul Society.
Do you feel it?
The pulsation of my power…
The power of the one
who shall punish you!
Is that the same technique
that Urahara told me about?
You seem confused.
I know what you're thinking,
so I shall give you
a definitive answer.
It's something entirely different.
The Quincy Letz Stile that you know
is a relic of the past
that died out 200 years ago
due to its fragile nature.
The only one who was attached to it
was Soken Ishida,
who rejected our research
and evolution!
By comparison,
this Quincy Voll Stern Dich…
the difference in power is
as far apart as heaven and earth!
I see…
I don't know about your history,
but in short,
it's different from Ishida's power.
I'm glad to hear that.
If Ishida transformed into
something as creepy as that…
I might cut him down by mistake.
You're easing up on your blade.
Getsugatensho!
That's not good.
You should aim your strikes.
Damn it!
That said, even if you did that,
you wouldn't find any weaknesses!
You called this form of mine
creepy, didn't you?
That is the correct response.
To the eyes of you
atrocious Soul Reapers,
the form of we holy executioners…
should be creepy and horrifying
to behold!
No way!
Sotenkishun is being peeled away!
Now have a taste…
of my Voll Stern Dich,
the power of Piskiel!
What…?!
What is that monster?
You assumed
we couldn't fight anymore,
so you let down your guard,
didn't you?
I thought we told you that
you shouldn't underestimate us…
Show this cocky four-eyed monkey
your power!
Ayon!
What the hell…
is that thing?!
Ayon is a monster created through
the fusion of our left arms!
He's got power,
but he's unpredictable!
A monster like you could never
beat my Voll Stern Dich--!
ISHIDA RESIDENCE - ARCHIVES
There's nothing of importance here…
What are you doing?
Ryuken!
I thought I told you
not to come in here
without my permission.
The Soul Society and Hueco Mundo
are being invaded by someone.
And they are most likely…Quincies.
There shouldn't be any Quincies
in existence aside from us.
Do you know something about this?!
This has nothing to do with you.
- Get out.
- Are you going to avoid me again?!
I am the last Quincy.
I have a right to know
what's going on.
The answer you seek…
cannot be found here.
SHORYU GATE ENTRANCE
Shino, I know this probably isn't
the best time to ask this, but…
What is it?
Do you happen to know why
Soul Reapers and Quincies
are at odds with each other
in the first place?
We both share the same goal
of defeating Hollows, don't we?
What?!
That's because…
Wait…
Why is that?
You know that in ancient times,
Soul Reapers were referred to
as Balancers, don't you?
S…
SQUAD 13 SIXTH SEAT -
HIDETOMO KAJOMARU
Sixth Seat Kajomaru!
It's an honor to see you here!
Well, the alarms
haven't sounded yet,
so why don't we discuss this a bit?
For starters,
you understand the law of
this world where souls circulate
between the World of the Living
and the Soul Society, don't you?
- Yes.
- Of course!
Good.
However, souls that become Hollows
in the World of the Living
cannot return to the Soul Society.
By purifying Hollows and delivering
their souls to the Soul Society,
they are led back to
the normal circulation of souls.
This is the job of Soul Reapers
and the reason why
we are called Balancers.
However, Quincies destroy
and completely extinguish
souls that have become Hollows.
What happens when they do that?
The souls are unable to return
to the Soul Society?
That's right.
Normally,
a balance must be maintained
between the number of souls
that exist in the Soul Society
and the World of the Living.
As Quincies extinguish more Hollows
in the World of the Living,
the number of souls is diminished,
disrupting that natural balance…
If we allow this to happen,
the balance of souls
will eventually be ruined,
causing the Soul Society to flow
into the World of the Living…
ending in the simultaneous
destruction of both worlds.
There isn't much written
about Quincies to begin with…
Master…
"Cannot be found here…"
ISHIDA RESIDENCE -
RYUKEN ISHIDA'S ROOM
This is Master's--!
To prevent this destruction,
the Soul Society had repeatedly
approached the Quincies
for a dialogue,
but they were turned away
each time.
The world was steadily
heading toward destruction.
And after endless debate
within the Soul Society…
the Quincy Extermination Operation
was finally carried out
200 years ago.
Our goals do not mesh
and the grudge borne of
their genocide will never perish.
The Soul Reapers and Quincies
have no other choice but to fight…
Do you understand,
Squad Member Ryunosuke Yuki?
May I…ask one question?
Are we Soul Reapers
fighting this battle for justice?
If there is justice
on one side or the other,
it would be called self-defense
or conquest.
However, this is a war.
Wars take place…
because both sides are just.
You know why I've called you here,
don't you,
SQUAD 1 BARRACKS -
HEAD CAPTAIN'S OFFICE
Squad 12 Captain Kurotsuchi?
Is this about mobilizing
members of Squad 12
to expunge 28,000 citizens
of the Rukon District
without permission in order to
correct the balance of souls?
Why didn't you get permission?
Those mass disappearances
in the Rukon District
reported by Squad 11's
Third Seat Ikkaku Madarame
and Fifth Seat Yumichika Ayasegawa…
You would have gotten permission
if things became dire.
The mass extermination of Hollows
in the World of the Living
by the rebel army was intentionally
done to disrupt the balance
between the World of the Living
and the Soul Society.
If you consider the fact that
the lives of the people
of the Rukon District stopped
the collapse of both worlds,
it is not that big of a loss.
If I had waited for permission
and the situation had escalated
beyond control,
that is not something
I could take responsibility for.
But if your Department of
Research and Development
had reported the matter
and promptly dealt with it,
we might have prevented
the current situation.
You're wrong about that.
The moment that the Quincy
known as Uryu Ishida
infiltrated the Soul Society
as a Ryoka,
I had already foreseen this would
happen and had given my advice.
You are the one who chose
to needlessly disregard my words.
Everything that is happening now
stems from the fact that
you, Head Captain,
couldn't kill that man
1,000 years ago!
Oh, dear.
But man, this guy's tough.
I can't believe
he's still in one piece
after that beating
he took from Ayon--
Impressive…
The report did not indicate
this kind of power…
I must advise His Majesty
to adjust the strength of our Blut.
But before I do that…
Each and every one of you…
will die here immediately.
Not again?!
Actually…
Wait, Ayon!
Stop!
Perhaps I should say,
"you will live here."
Sklave Rai.
A Quincy's basic ability
to focus Reishi.
When taken to its highest limits,
it becomes the absolute
subordination of Reishi.
If possible,
I didn't want to use it…
because my holy wings would be
tarnished by such wicked beings.
A wise decision.
However,
you've neglected to take
the difference in our power
into consideration.
Inoue!
Sado!
Whenever I see such a struggle,
it reaffirms my beliefs.
Is the sight of the weak dying
always so unsightly?
I cannot stand to watch this.
Die.
A Bankai…!
If I destroy the disk on your head…
you can't use that absolute
subordination of Reishi anymore,
can you?!
Figuring that out is one thing.
But to actually go for it
takes courage…!
You really are…
difficult to deal with,
aren't you?!
Hurry!
Hurry it up!
Oh, come on,
what are you talking about?!
You're the one who said,
"We should save Dondochakka"
"while Ichigo Kurosaki is
distracting the enemy!"
That was a close one!
I didn't think we would have to
go through this much trouble!
Not only are you heavy
but you chose to hide in the sand!
That hurts!
Don't enter without my permission.
This is the second time.
What's the meaning of this?
Are the things written here true?
I guess that means
you know everything…
About the Wandenreich…
About the guy
referred to as "His Majesty"…
And even about Mom…!
Uryu…
This has nothing to do with you.
There's no need to be so tense.
Sixth Seat Kajomaru…
Squad 11 is standing by
outside the gate.
There's no need to worry.
- What was that?!
- There's a blue light!
What's going on?!
Conflict is such
an unpleasant affair.
SQUAD SIX BARRACKS
- What's that?!
-Is it an enemy attack?!
SQUAD EIGHT BARRACKS - ENGAWA
SQUAD NINE BARRACKS -
EDITORIAL DEPARTMENT
SQUAD THREE'S GUARD AREA
SQUAD SIX'S GUARD AREA
What the hell…is this?
SQUAD THIRTEEN'S GUARD AREA
Flaming pillars…of Reishi?
SQUAD 1 THIRD SEAT -
GENSHIRO OKIKIBA
SQUAD 3 THIRD SEAT - RIKU TOGAKUSHI
SQUAD 3 FIFTH SEAT - TAKETSUNA GORI
SQUAD 3 SIXTH SEAT - ASUKA KATAKURA
Reishi Investigation Team!
How much longer?!
Spiritual Pressure detected!
A 93 percent match!
It's a Quincy!
Lieutenant Kira!
How dare you launch
a surprise attack!
Spiral and Rise, Shunjin!
Blow, Mogaribue!
Counteract, Katakage!
Sorry…
but our orders are to kill you all.
Tremble in fear, Soul Reapers.
The Stern Ritters are going to…
purge all of you.
Everything we had left behind
Our breaths blending as mist
without form or expression
We lie buried as we glare
into the distance
I can't hear anything
I can't seem to cut anything
It feels like I'm sinking
Falling, falling
Touching
Eyes struck wide open
Something no one has ever seen
The furthest reaches are now visible to us
It cannot be undone
and cannot be stopped
This ensuing struggle
Whisk it away beyond
the ends of the earth
Along with our breaths
Take everything
Whisk it away beyond
the ends of the earth
Along with our futures
Along with our world
Something no one has ever seen
The furthest reaches are now
visible to us
Don't you know God's demand?
As we tear each other down
"A frostbitten world turns to fire,
a shadow of a wing remains."
"I try and try again,
it slips away, shadow of a wing."